ANDREAS SOSILO

MSc., Dipl.-Ing. (FH)

PROFILE

I am a creative and hardworking Junior Full Stack Web Developer with interest and skills in web development using JavaScript, React, Node.js, HTML and CSS.

I discovered my passion for coding while I was working as automation engineer, in which I worked with PLC programming, C++ and C#.

Driven by my interest to build sophisticated and cutting-edge web applications, I joined Hacktiv8 Coding Bootcamp to focus my career on web development.

CONTACT

+49 176 821 268 42 /

+62 811 991 123

□ andreas.sosilo@gmail.com

github.com/andreassosilo

in linkedin.com/in/andreassosilo

andreassosilo.github.io

OTHERS

Born in Indonesia, 14/03/1987 Indonesian, Blue Card EU German Car Driving License (Klasse B)

EDUCATION

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER PROGRAM

HACKTIV8 | 2019 - 2019

• Full-time coding bootcamp in web development.

MASTER OF SCIENCE IN MECHATRONICS

UNIVERSITÄT SIEGEN | 2010 - 2013

• GPA: 1.8 good (German grade).

DIPL.-ING. (FH) IN ENGINEERING & PROJECT MANAGEMENT, S.T. (BACHELOR) IN MECHATRONICS

SWISS GERMAN UNIVERSITY, FH SÜDWESTFALEN | 2005 - 2009

• GPA: 3.48/4.00 good (English grade).

SKILLS

- JavaScript
- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap
- React, Redux, React Native
- Node.js, Express.js, REST API
- MochaJS, ChaiJS, JEST, TDD
- MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Redis
- Amazon Web Service
- Git, Github
- Scrum

- German (Niveau B2)
- English (fluent)
- Indonesian (native)

EXPERIENCE

OPERATIONAL & MECHANIZATION SUB-DEPT HEAD / AUTOMATION ENGINEER

TRIPUTRA GROUP | MAR 2017 - JUN 2019

- Industry: mining, agribusiness, manufacturing.
- Automation engineering.
- (Automation) process improvement and optimization.
- Project management (timeline, resources, cost).

CUSTOMER SERVICE COORDINATOR / FIELD SERVICE ENGINEER

KRONES AG | OCT 2014 - FEB 2017

- Industry: packaging for bottled drinks.
- Automation engineering.
- PLC programming (Siemens S7, WinCC).
- Project management (timeline, resources, cost).

INTERN

KAMAT PUMPEN GMBH & CO. KG | MAR 2008 - AUG 2008

• Industry: high pressure pumps.

AWARDS

TRIPUTRA GROUP

BEST MANAGEMENT TRAINEE 2017-2018